KRISTINA RAJA RÉSUMÉ

→ Home: 613.422.9080 → Mobile: 613.293.4664

→ Email: kristinarajaphoto@gmail.com

→ Website: kristinaraja.com

PROFILE

Studied for three years at Dawson College in Professional Photography and is a graduate from Algonquin College with a certificate in Interactive Multimedia. Kristina has experienced with HTML, CSS, WordPress, jQuery, PHP and the Adobe Creative Suite.

Kristina has a strong work ethic and prides herself on being determined, organized, professional and creative. She is inspired and driven by modern influences in pop culture. Kristina is able to work well with others and can also handle independent projects. Apart from being in front of a computer screen, Kristina enjoys social networking, traveling, Starbucks coffee, cooking, and cats.

Looking for a position as a Graphic Designer, Web Designer, or UX/UI Designer.

EXPERIENCE

The Royal College of Physicians and Surgeons of Canada, Ottawa, ON

Web Content Designer
September 2014 – present
CMS(Oracle) maintenance, updating website
content, trouble shooting errors and testing
software using Adobe Dreamweaver. Designing
and re-formatting graphic elements for the web
using Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop and Adobe
InDesign.

The Ottawa Hospital Foundation, Ottawa, ON

Web Integration Developer August 2014 – August 2014 CMS(Drupal) maintenance, updating website content, YouTube maintenance, trouble shooting errors and testing software. Designing and reformatting graphic elements for the web; photo editing, sliders and Evites. Produced Digital Signage for the foundation using Adobe After Effects.

Ottawa General Contractors, Ottawa, ON

Intern Graphic Designer

June 2014 – August 2014

Created and prepared layouts for a variety of flyers, sales inserts, vectors, posters, banners, icons, folders, and with Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop & InDesign. Produced Flash Ads using Adobe Flash and Illustrator for Google AdWords.

Vidrack, Ottawa, ON

Freelance Graphic/Web Designer April 2014 – present Freelance consultant and graphic/web designer fixing and updating Vidrack's WordPress website using HTML & CSS and WordPress Plugins as well as creating vectors using Adobe Illustrator.

Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON

Program Assistant

January 2014 – April 2014

Program Assistant for the Interactive Multimedia
Post-Grad students. Aiding and tutoring the
students with JavaScript, WordPress, PHP and
MySQL assignments and projects.

Boast Technologies, Ottawa, ON

Graphic/Web Designer July 2013 – April 2014
Sole graphic designer in charge of developing both static and WordPress websites for clients by coding with HTML, CSS, jQuery. Quality
Assurance tools include: responsive design, cross-browser compatibility, inspect element, Sublime Text, Balsamiq, Adobe fireworks, Fluid UI, and Solidify App. Created a variety of vectors, posters, banners, icons, business cards, logos, folders, and flyers with Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop & InDesign.

Magnitis Software Solutions, Montreal, QC

Freelance Graphic Designer

April 2013 – May 2013

Freelance consultant and graphic/web designer designing three different sized icons and a banner for an app on the Google Play Store called "Ghost (Fitness) Trainer". Icons were made using Adobe Illustrator.

Client Work, Montreal, QC

Freelance Photographer

September 2009 – June 2012

Photographing both studio and on location shots for several clients who received retouched photos and digital copies. Post-production was done in Adobe Photoshop.

Client, Montreal, QC

Freelance Videographer
June 2010 – August 2010

Filmed a wedding video using an HD camcorder and a spot microphone. Clients received an edited copy on a DVD-R. Final Cut Pro was used for post-production. Post-production was done in Adobe Photoshop.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Adobe Creative Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, InDesign, Acrobat, Premier, Lightroom, Bridge, Flash, After Effects, and Fireworks.
- Web: HTML, CSS, WordPress, JavaScript/jQuery, PHP, MySQL, ActionScript, and Web APIs.
- Microsoft Office Collection: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Outlook.
- Operating Systems: MAC OS X, Windows 7 & 8, and Linux.
- Other: Balsamiq, Solidify App, Sublime Text, Final Cut Pro, GitHub, Bitbucket.

PROJECTS

Gojournalism.ca Website

A crowdsourcing website for journalists and writers who want get their ideas heard. Revamping their website in order to create a better user experience and attractive design using WordPress, HTML & CSS.

A Nature Minute - Class Project

Filmed and produced a 30 second PSA about Ontario's Nature using a Canon T1i and a tripod. Post-Production done in Adobe Premiere.

Kristinaraja.com Website

Created a modern, sleek design and a responsive website using HTML, CSS and jQuery for a self- promotional photography website.

Cat Dress Up - Class Project

Created a cat-themed dress-up game using Adobe Flash and coded in AcrionScript 3. Vectors were made using Adobe Illustrator.

VOLUNTEERING

Arbitrage Magazine, Ottawa, ON

Graphic Designer

April 2014 – August 2014

Assigned to create banners for articles (both vector and non-vector) using Adobe Illustrator and Photoshop.

EDUCATION

Interactive Multimedia

Algonquin College, Ottawa, ON. September 2012 to April 2013

Professional Photography

Dawson College, Montreal, QC. August 2009 – June 2012

LANGUAGES

- English
- French